<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- Privacy Policy Strings -->
    <string name="last_updated">Last updated</string>
    <string name="privacy_info_collect_title">1. Information We Collect</string>
    <string name="privacy_info_collect_desc">TaskMaster collects the following information to provide you with our task management services:</string>
    <string name="privacy_account_info">Account Information</string>
    <string name="privacy_account_info_desc">Email address, display name, and profile picture</string>
    <string name="privacy_task_data">Task Data</string>
    <string name="privacy_task_data_desc">Task titles, descriptions, due dates, priorities, and completion status</string>
    <string name="privacy_app_usage">App Usage</string>
    <string name="privacy_app_usage_desc">Settings preferences, language selection, and theme preferences</string>
    <string name="privacy_device_info">Device Information</string>
    <string name="privacy_device_info_desc">Device type, operating system version, and app version</string>
    <string name="privacy_how_use_title">2. How We Use Your Information</string>
    <string name="privacy_how_use_desc">We use your information to:</string>
    <string name="privacy_use_item1">Provide and maintain our task management services</string>
    <string name="privacy_use_item2">Sync your data across devices</string>
    <string name="privacy_use_item3">Personalize your app experience</string>
    <string name="privacy_use_item4">Send you important updates about the app</string>
    <string name="privacy_use_item5">Improve our services and develop new features</string>
    <string name="privacy_storage_title">3. Data Storage and Security</string>
    <string name="privacy_storage_desc">Your data is stored securely using Firebase, which provides enterprise-grade security. We implement appropriate technical and organizational measures to protect your personal information against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure, or destruction.</string>
    <string name="privacy_sharing_title">4. Data Sharing</string>
    <string name="privacy_sharing_desc">We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your personal information to third parties without your consent, except as described in this privacy policy. We may share your information only in the following circumstances:</string>
    <string name="privacy_sharing_item1">With your explicit consent</string>
    <string name="privacy_sharing_item2">To comply with legal obligations</string>
    <string name="privacy_sharing_item3">To protect our rights and prevent fraud</string>
    <string name="privacy_rights_title">5. Your Rights</string>
    <string name="privacy_rights_desc">You have the right to:</string>
    <string name="privacy_rights_item1">Access your personal data</string>
    <string name="privacy_rights_item2">Correct inaccurate data</string>
    <string name="privacy_rights_item3">Delete your account and data</string>
    <string name="privacy_rights_item4">Export your data</string>
    <string name="privacy_rights_item5">Withdraw consent at any time</string>
    <string name="privacy_retention_title">6. Data Retention</string>
    <string name="privacy_retention_desc">We retain your personal information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you with our services. You can delete your account at any time, and we will delete your data within 30 days.</string>
    <string name="privacy_children_title">7. Children\'s Privacy</string>
    <string name="privacy_children_desc">Our services are not intended for children under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13.</string>
    <string name="privacy_changes_title">8. Changes to This Policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_changes_desc">We may update this privacy policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new privacy policy in the app and updating the "Last updated" date.</string>
    <string name="contact_us">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="privacy_contact_desc">If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us at:</string>
    <string name="address">Address</string>
    <string name="address_value">Rosebank College, South Africa</string>
    
    <!-- Terms of Service Strings -->
    <string name="terms_important">Important</string>
    <string name="terms_important_note">By using TaskMaster, you agree to be bound by these Terms of Service. Please read them carefully.</string>
    <string name="terms_acceptance_title">1. Acceptance of Terms</string>
    <string name="terms_acceptance_desc">By downloading, installing, or using the TaskMaster mobile application ("App"), you agree to be bound by these Terms of Service ("Terms"). If you do not agree to these Terms, please do not use our App.</string>
    <string name="terms_description_title">2. Description of Service</string>
    <string name="terms_description_desc">TaskMaster is a task management application that allows users to:</string>
    <string name="terms_service_item1">Create, edit, and organize tasks</string>
    <string name="terms_service_item2">Set due dates and priorities</string>
    <string name="terms_service_item3">Track task completion status</string>
    <string name="terms_service_item4">Sync data across multiple devices</string>
    <string name="terms_service_item5">Customize app settings and preferences</string>
    <string name="terms_accounts_title">3. User Accounts</string>
    <string name="terms_accounts_desc">To use TaskMaster, you must create an account by providing accurate and complete information. You are responsible for:</string>
    <string name="terms_accounts_item1">Maintaining the confidentiality of your account credentials</string>
    <string name="terms_accounts_item2">All activities that occur under your account</string>
    <string name="terms_accounts_item3">Notifying us immediately of any unauthorized use</string>
    <string name="terms_accounts_item4">Ensuring your account information remains accurate and up-to-date</string>
    <string name="terms_acceptable_title">4. Acceptable Use</string>
    <string name="terms_acceptable_desc">You agree to use TaskMaster only for lawful purposes and in accordance with these Terms. You agree NOT to:</string>
    <string name="terms_acceptable_item1">Use the App for any illegal or unauthorized purpose</string>
    <string name="terms_acceptable_item2">Attempt to gain unauthorized access to our systems</string>
    <string name="terms_acceptable_item3">Interfere with or disrupt the App\'s functionality</string>
    <string name="terms_acceptable_item4">Upload malicious code or harmful content</string>
    <string name="terms_acceptable_item5">Violate any applicable laws or regulations</string>
    <string name="terms_ip_title">5. Intellectual Property</string>
    <string name="terms_ip_desc">The TaskMaster App, including its design, functionality, and content, is protected by intellectual property laws. You may not:</string>
    <string name="terms_ip_item1">Copy, modify, or distribute the App</string>
    <string name="terms_ip_item2">Reverse engineer or attempt to extract source code</string>
    <string name="terms_ip_item3">Use our trademarks or logos without permission</string>
    <string name="terms_ip_item4">Create derivative works based on our App</string>
    <string name="terms_data_title">6. Data and Privacy</string>
    <string name="terms_data_desc">Your privacy is important to us. Please review our Privacy Policy to understand how we collect, use, and protect your information. By using our App, you consent to the collection and use of your data as described in our Privacy Policy.</string>
    <string name="terms_availability_title">7. Service Availability</string>
    <string name="terms_availability_desc">We strive to provide reliable service, but we cannot guarantee that the App will be available at all times. We may:</string>
    <string name="terms_availability_item1">Perform maintenance and updates</string>
    <string name="terms_availability_item2">Experience technical difficulties</string>
    <string name="terms_availability_item3">Modify or discontinue features</string>
    <string name="terms_availability_item4">Suspend service for security reasons</string>
    <string name="terms_liability_title">8. Limitation of Liability</string>
    <string name="terms_liability_desc">To the maximum extent permitted by law, TaskMaster and its developers shall not be liable for any indirect, incidental, special, consequential, or punitive damages, including but not limited to loss of profits, data, or use, arising from your use of the App.</string>
    <string name="terms_termination_title">9. Termination</string>
    <string name="terms_termination_desc">We may terminate or suspend your account at any time, with or without notice, for any reason, including violation of these Terms. You may also terminate your account at any time by deleting the App and contacting us.</string>
    <string name="terms_changes_title">10. Changes to Terms</string>
    <string name="terms_changes_desc">We reserve the right to modify these Terms at any time. We will notify users of significant changes through the App or other means. Your continued use of the App after changes constitutes acceptance of the new Terms.</string>
    <string name="terms_governing_title">11. Governing Law</string>
    <string name="terms_governing_desc">These Terms are governed by the laws of South Africa. Any disputes arising from these Terms or your use of the App will be subject to the jurisdiction of South African courts.</string>
    <string name="contact_information">Contact Information</string>
    <string name="terms_contact_desc">If you have any questions about these Terms of Service, please contact us:</string>
    <string name="phone">Phone</string>
    <string name="phone_value">+27 (0) 11 123 4567</string>
</resources>

